A Guide to the Papers of the Secretary of the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia, 1975-1999
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Secretary of the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia 1975-1999
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/2/1.022
This collection consists of 1,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred by the Office of the Board of Visitors, The Rotunda, University of Virginia on 2002 October 21.
Biographical/Historical Information
During the time span of these papers, Alexander G. Gilliam, Jr. (1991- ) held the position of Secretary to the Board of Visitors.
Scope and Content Information
The papers consist of general records, including correspondence, memoranda, and related papers.
Contents List
- I: General Files 1976-1999
  - Alexander G. Gilliam-Fraternity/Sorority Housing Task Force 1983, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - International Studies-Memos to Peter Hackett 1988-1991 (Box 1)
  - International Exchanges-Yunnen 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Maison Francaise 1985-1990, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - P.E.N. Meeting 1980-1985 (Box 1)
  - White Burkett Miller Center of Public Affairs 1979-1984 (Box 1)
  - Kidney Stone Machine Proposal 1983 (Box 2)
  - President of Nicaragua 1979-1999 (Box 2)
  - Akashi 1998 (Box 2)
  - Sugar Bowl 1990 (Box 2)
  - Alexander G. Gilliam 1977-1982 (Box 2)
  - House Bill #547 1976 (Box 2)
  - Hoskins Field 1988-1994 (Box 2)
  - Georgetown Leadership Seminar 1996 (Box 2)
  - Fulbright Dinner 1995 (Box 2)
  - Finals 1999 (Box 3)
  - Afro-American Affairs-Carter G. Woodson Institute 1986 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Affairs 1981 (Box 3)
  - Aushwitz Haberfield House 1994 (Box 3)
  - Australia 1992 (Box 3)
  - Barrett 1990 (Box 3)
  - Byrd Portrait 1995 (Box 3)
  - Finals 1997 (Box 3)
  - Admissions-General 1988-1990 (Box 3)
  - General Assembly Members 1976-1983 (Box 3)
- II: Restricted Files 1988-1994 (Box 4)